Guide to the Richard Erdoes Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- 2010 Addition, 1920-2008; 49.08; (121 boxes) + 1 broadside
  - Correspondence and Papers Relating to Activism, 1910-2008; Series II; 12.09; (29 boxes)
    - "A Woman Called Hatter Fox," Joanelle Nadine Romero et al., 1982, 1994 (Box 271)
    - Richard Lancaster, 1984-1987 (Box 271)
    - Lame Deer designs, undated (Box 271)
    - Nuclear fuel, 1979, undated (Box 271)
    - Mary Thunder, 1991 (Box 271)
    - Aquash-Kamook, 2004 (Box 271)
    - Water rights, environmental issues, 2003-2005 (Box 271)
    - Annie Mae Aquash, 1995, undated (Box 271)
    - Sioux medicine man speaks, 1976 (Box 271)
    - First Nation war veterans, 1994 November 4 (Box 271)
    - Tash's story, "Shii Noa Shoa", 2002 (Box 271)
    - Picus Verlag, 1998-1999 (Box 272)
    - "Peltier reviewed for parole", 2000 (Box 272)
    - Vine Deloria, undated (Box 272)
    - Black Elk, 2004 (Box 272)
    - Nilak Butler, 2002 (Box 272)
    - Bob Free-Peltier, 2002-2003 (Box 272)
    - Bear Butte, 2003 (Box 272)
    - Carter Camp, 2002 (Box 272)
    - Wounded Knee memoir, typescript, corrected, 1st page, 2003 (Box 272)
    - Niese, 2002 (Box 272)
    - Synopsis, undated (Box 272)
    - Peltiers operation, 2000 (Box 272)
    - Siberians, Reindeer, undated (Box 272)
    - Stig Thornson, 1982 (Box 272)
    - Innu, 2001 (Box 272)
    - Peltier, 2003 (Box 272)
    - Momaday, 1993 (Box 272)
    - Rituals - Pueblo and Navajo quotes, undated (Box 272)
    - Unidentified partial typescript, undated (Box 272)
    - Crow Dog creation, 1971 (Box 272)
    - Washinawatok, 1999 (Box 272)
    - Oglala Tribe, 1998 February (Box 272)
    - Annie Mae, David Seals, 1999 (Box 272)
    - Article [or IMA], 1999 (Box 272)
    - IMAI article, undated (Box 272)
    - Griffin script, 1978-1986 (Box 272)
    - Lame Deer, undated (Box 272)
    - "Sister Hidden", undated (Box 272)
    - Media Degree Program at Oglala Lakota College, 2001 (Box 272)
    - Steve Hendricks, 2006 (Box 272)
    - The defenestration of Frankie Shooter, 2005 (Box 272)
    - Baxter script (photocopy), undated (Box 272)
    - Symposium on Buffalo Jumps, undated (Box 273)
    - Photographs and "Ground-flattening and Give-away", undated (Box 273)
    - Official Statements - Hurd quote, undated (Box 273)
    - Montezuma headdress, undated (Box 273)
    - Len Foster, 1998 March 27 (Box 273)
    - Addenda, undated (Box 273)
    - Banks! Now, undated (Box 273)
    - Yellow Bird, 2002 August (Box 273)
    - Red Shirt Black Hills, undated (Box 273)
    - Wounded Knee - Dennis - Photo, 1973-2000 (Box 273)
    - Indian, 2002-2003 (Box 273)
    - Dennis Banks, 1984, undated (Box 273)
    - Owen Luck, 1973 (Box 273)
    - The Custer Trials, 1974 (Box 273)
    - Notes on Crow Dog film, undated (Box 273)
    - Lomahi Aftewa[?], 1994, 2000 (Box 273)
    - "Indigenous people - Nader", 2000 (Box 273)
    - Shamans, 1989-1992, undated (Box 273)
    - Odd pages, 1978, undated (Box 273)
    - Women book, undated (Box 273)
    - Snips, undated (Box 273)
    - Anna Mae, 2004 (Box 273)
    - Freedom's Daughters - Lynn Olson, 2003-2004, undated (Box 273)
    - Indian books, slides, 1974-1980 (Box 273)
    - Saloon manuscript, undated (Box 273)
    - Civil rights, general, 1978-1979 (Box 273)
    - Alan Cooper, 2007, undated (Box 274)
    - Letter to Judge Merhige, undated (Box 274)
    - Dennis: Fun at the Knee, 1973 October 17 (Box 274)
    - Oglala shoot out 1975, 1975-1979 (Box 274)
    - Correspondence and typescripts, 1990-1993 (Box 274)
    - Periodicals and newsletters, 1991-2004 (Box 274)
    - IMAI captions, undated (Box 274)
    - Rights fund, 1978-1983 (Box 274)
    - Miscellanous, 1914-2007; 2 (Box 274)
    - Legislation culture, undated (Box 274)
    - Anonymous on CD's Paradise, undated (Box 274)
    - Indian maps, undated (Box 274)
    - Lamedeer flight, 1877, undated (Box 274)
    - "What Really Happened at Little Bighorn", 1990-1992 (Box 274)
    - Lumby, undated (Box 274)
    - Medicine wheel article, 1990 (Box 274)
    - Kickapod Sagwa, undated (Box 274)
    - Mt. Kinley mine, undated (Box 275)
    - Pit River, undated (Box 275)
    - Piscataway, 1979-1982 (Box 275)
    - Newspapers and magazines, 1974-1995; 7 (Box 275)
    - Newspapers and magazines, 1969-1992, undated (Box 276)
    - Pre-history, 1964-1993 (Box 276)
    - Indian historical, undated (Box 276)
    - Masks, undated (Box 276)
    - Pueblos, New Mexico, 1970-1975 (Box 276)
    - "A Pueblo Woman Speaks", undated (Box 276)
    - Huichol Peyote, undated (Box 276)
    - Indian bike ride, undated (Box 276)
    - Indian Steps Museum, undated (Box 276)
    - Iroquois, Six Nations, Mohawks, 1969-1979 (Box 276)
    - Klamath, 1974 (Box 276)
    - Indians, Latin America, 1982, undated (Box 276)
    - Erich, 1981 (Box 276)
    - Ballard, undated (Box 276)
    - Doris Burnette poems, 1980 (Box 276)
    - Small boy, 1968 (Box 276)
    - Mt. Cloud, 1976 June 4 (Box 276)
    - ADI Defender, 1975-1976 (Box 276)
    - Miscellaneous, 2001, undated (Box 276)
    - "Fried Bread for President," excerpt, 1983 (Box 276)
    - "Look into the Heart", circa 1994 (Box 276)
    - Lella Russell Smith, undated (Box 276)
    - The Legend of the Earth Children, undated (Box 276)
    - Untitled short story, undated (Box 276)
    - Dennis Banks writings/reviews, 1996-2004 (Box 277)
    - Dennis letters, 1985 (Box 277)
    - Banks, 1994 (Box 277)
    - Annie Mae controversy; "Warning Signs", 2002, undated (Box 277)
    - "The Coyote Bead," and untitled typescripts, 1999, undated (Box 277)
    - Walk for justice, 1994 (Box 277)
    - Wassaya, 1976 (Box 277)
    - Annie Mae letter, Oregon, 1999 December 22 (Box 277)
    - Custer's revenge, outrageous video play, undated (Box 277)
    - Interview with Dennis Banks, Santa Cruz, 1992 (Box 277)
    - Chubbs, Tokala, 2000 April 18 (Box 277)
    - Banks, undated (Box 277)
    - Onondaga, 1982 (Box 277)
    - Dennis Banks songs, still strong, undated (Box 277)
    - Indian potpourri, 1982-2000 (Box 277)
    - Peltier, 2000 (Box 277)
    - "Nineteenth-century Ledger Drawings" and "Yanomami: What have we done to them?", 2000 (Box 277)
    - Banks, Sante Fe video, 1990 (Box 277)
    - Kamook, undated (Box 277)
    - "When Activists Attack!", 2000 (Box 277)
    - Dennis and the drum, 1973 (Box 277)
    - Dennis Banks on women, 1992-1996 (Box 277)
    - National Committee on Indian Work of the Episcopal Church newsletter and Bandelier map/guide, 1973 (Box 277)
    - Dennis - Custer, 1973-1975 (Box 278)
    - Thomas Benyacya, undated (Box 278)
    - Sundance protocol, Lightningbolt letter, Native American Report 10/6/97, clipping, 1997 October 6 (Box 278)
    - Fortunate Eagle, 1991, 1996 (Box 278)
    - Institute of American Arts publicity, 1977 February (Box 278)
    - Where do we go from here?, undated (Box 278)
    - Various writings, Rundbrief, notes, undated (Box 278)
    - Indianische Gedichte, 1974 February (Box 278)
    - "Sister Hidden," Cy Griffin, 1995, undated (Box 278)
    - Sacred Run, 1993-1996 (Box 278)
    - Pete Catches, 1970 (Box 278)
    - Banks arrest in Mexico, 1976 (Box 278)
    - Dennis on tolerance, 1987 (Box 278)
    - Dennis Banks, 1973-1974 (Box 278)
    - Proposal, AIM history, undated (Box 278)
    - Printed report, 1996 (Box 278)
    - Dennis Banks material, Rapid City, undated (Box 278)
    - Ojibwa history, Dennis, undated (Box 278)
    - Dennis Banks, undated (Box 278)
    - Extradition, 1976, undated (Box 278)
    - Coke Millard, undated (Box 278)
    - Dennis Banks - personal remarks - letter to me, 1976, undated (Box 278)
    - Banks, Native Peoples' 100 year plan, undated (Box 278)
    - Dennis, Oregon, 1976 (Box 278)
    - Native American Policy newsletter, 2000 (Box 278)
    - Banks' pleading, Oregon - Pleads guilty - Gets parole, undated (Box 278)
    - Take-over, Naval air station, 1971, undated (Box 278)
    - Michelle Vignes, 1983 June 6 (Box 278)
    - Trials, general - Case against government, 1975 (Box 278)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995-1996, undated (Box 279)
    - Banks - Means trial, 1973-1976 (Box 279)
    - Dennis Banks in prison, undated (Box 279)
    - Banks in California, 1974-1975 (Box 279)
    - Banks, Peltier, 1996-1998 (Box 279)
    - Dennis on women, undated (Box 279)
    - Memo re: Order form and how to subscribe to Akwesasne, notes, undated (Box 279)
    - Dennis' FBI Files, 1995, undated (Box 279)
    - Education Issues - Dennis Banks, 1970 (Box 279)
    - Fair and Equal Justice - Tilsen, undated (Box 279)
    - Banks - Means trials, middle, 1974 (Box 279)
    - Names of trial supporters, 1976 (Box 279)
    - Means - Banks trial transcripts, undated (Box 279)
    - Banks freedom notes, 1984-1986 (Box 279)
    - Leonard Peltier, 1976-1996; 2 (Box 279)
    - Winona LaDuke, 1996, undated (Box 279)
    - "Legend of the Dream Catcher" and "Beaver and "Porcupine" (Thompson 1928), undated (Box 279)
    - Older AIM, undated (Box 279)
    - Various Native American folk tales, 1999, undated (Box 279)
    - Photocopies of photographs of Native American men, undated (Box 280)
    - Poetry, 1971-1973 (Box 280)
    - White Buffalo Woman, 1977 November (Box 280)
    - Butler - Robideau, 1974 (Box 280)
    - "Dog Soldiers", 1977 December 1 (Box 280)
    - Interview: young Indian woman, undated (Box 280)
    - Helene Hagan - Archetypal ethnology newsletter, 1990-1992 (Box 280)
    - Jean: "Sioux east", undated (Box 280)
    - Banks proposal, undated (Box 280)
    - AIM annual report, 1970 February (Box 280)
    - Akwesasne Notes, 1973 April (Box 280)
    - Doug Durham on AIM, US Congress, 1994, undated (Box 280)
    - Russell Means interview, 1976 (Box 280)
    - How to do Mr. Indian in - AIM humor, undated (Box 280)
    - Dream Catcher, undated (Box 280)
    - Cy Griffin on Wounded Knee, undated (Box 280)
    - "The Indian Situation in the Summer of 1975," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 280)
    - Wallace and Grace - Black Elk, undated (Box 280)
    - Cy Griffin on Wounded Knee, 1998 (Box 280)
    - Bellecourt - Means conflict, 1994 (Box 280)
    - Recent AIM - Targets by dissidents - Russ vs. Clyde, 1993-1994 (Box 280)
    - Russell Means interview, 1975 (Box 280)
    - National Council of Churches - Dennis items, undated (Box 280)
    - Report on US vs. Banks, typescript, undated (Box 280)
    - AIM general, 1974-1976 (Box 280)
    - Dennis' Onondaga interview - Custer, Janklow etc., 1994 April 13 (Box 280)
    - Dennis Longhand, manuscript, undated (Box 280)
    - Erdoes' Banks letter, 1974-1988 (Box 281)
    - Proposal for AIM book, undated (Box 281)
    - AIM - A book proposal, undated (Box 281)
    - Dennis in Mexican Jail, 1973 (Box 281)
    - Cass Lake, undated (Box 281)
    - Dennis Banks papers, undated (Box 281)
    - Banks-Means trials, end, undated (Box 281)
    - AIM - Birth, 1973 (Box 281)
    - Dennis and SLA, Symbionese Liberation Army, undated (Box 281)
    - Dennis 1986 - Jail, Longman[?], 1984 (Box 281)
    - Crow Dog on Yellow Thunder, undated (Box 281)
    - Banks Means trial, early, 1975 (Box 281)
    - Dennis Banks, 1984 trial (Box 281)
    - "Brave Woman Food: Holds off FFos with Gun," manuscript, undated (Box 281)
    - Regarding photos - Dennis Banks, 1977 (Box 281)
    - Big Mountain letter - Dennis Banks, 1985 (Box 281)
    - Dennis, 1995 (Box 281)
    - Banks Zimmerman excerpts, undated (Box 281)
    - AIM Patches and stickers, undated (Box 281)
    - Indian Civil Rights - various photographs, 1972-1973, undated (Box 281)
    - Wounded Knee, 1972-1976 (Box 281)
    - Papers re: Wounded Knee, 1972-1991; 2 (Box 281)
    - Nee na wind, red school house, 1977-1978 (Box 282)
    - "Lakota Woman" shooting schedule, 1993 October 11 (Box 282)
    - Fiction and poetry publications, 1976-1993 (Box 282)
    - Publications relating to schools, 1975-1986 (Box 282)
    - Political/legal publications, 1976-1980; 3 (Box 282)
    - Miscellaneous publications, 1967-1975 (Box 283)
    - US vs. Leonard Crow Dog, 1975-1976 (Box 283)
    - Newspapers and other papers, 1973-1994; 3 (Box 283)
    - Gary Robinson, 2001-2003 (Box 283)
    - Titles - Chapter heads, undated (Box 283)
    - Prisons, undated (Box 283)
    - Owen Luck pixs, (photocopies), circa 1973 (Box 283)
    - Owen Luck, Wounded Knee, (photocopies), circa 1973 (Box 283)
    - Russell Means, undated (Box 284)
    - Language, undated (Box 284)
    - Caption quotes, undated (Box 284)
    - Henry Niese, 2000 October 13 (Box 284)
    - Peltier-Gordon, 2000-2001 (Box 284)
    - Black Elk, 1978 (Box 284)
    - Archie Fire, 2001 January 31 (Box 284)
    - Chris Spotted Eagle, 2000 (Box 284)
    - Rosebud Land - Senate documents, 1910 January 17 (Box 284)
    - Indian Country Blues - Joanelle Nadine Ramero, 1993 (Box 284)
    - Peltier, 2001-2002; 2 (Box 284)
    - John Reyes, 1999-2002 (Box 284)
    - Eda Gordon, 2000 (Box 284)
    - Indian Times, 2002 (Box 284)
    - Indian miscellaneous, 2002 (Box 284)
    - Shenandoah poems, undated (Box 284)
    - Ortiz, 1978-1989 (Box 284)
    - Bull Roarer, 1973 (Box 284)
    - Indian women article, undated (Box 284)
    - Indian film proposals, undated (Box 284)
    - Helga PHD dissertation, 1999 (Box 284)
    - EDA Gordon-Peltier, 2001-2002 (Box 284)
    - Lois Red Elk, undated (Box 284)
    - Yuri Mandaganov, undated (Box 284)
    - Lakota Country Times, 2 issues, 2008 (Box 284)
    - Newspaper clippings, 2001 (Box 284)
    - Russell Means, 2000-2001 (Box 285)
    - AIM, undated (Box 285)
    - 2 Native American newspapers, 1999-2001 (Box 285)
    - Bobby Lake, undated (Box 285)
    - [Indian ephemera], 2001-2002 (Box 285)
    - Peltier, 2001 (Box 285)
    - "Footsteps of Wisdom" booklet, undated (Box 285)
    - Wounded Knee airdrop, longhand, undated (Box 285)
    - Wounded Knee, end of siege, longhand, undated (Box 285)
    - Trial, 1975-1979 (Box 285)
    - Annie Mae Aquash - Trudell, undated (Box 285)
    - Assault on Paradise, 1975 September 5 (Box 285)
    - Bear manuscript, undated (Box 285)
    - Ruth Hunsinger obituary, 1995 (Box 285)
    - My photos, Akwesasne, 1978, undated (Box 285)
    - Archie Fire Lame Deer -letters to me, undated (Box 285)
    - Wounded knee manuscript, 1973 (Box 285)
    - Buddy Lamont Clearwater, manuscript, undated (Box 285)
    - John Trudell, 1974-1993 (Box 285)
    - Jean's Trudell letter, 1979 (Box 285)
    - Verna, Leonard Crow Dog, undated (Box 286)
    - A bird's eye view of the native movement, 1984, undated (Box 286)
    - Lizzy Fast Horse, undated (Box 286)
    - Crow Dog poems, 1975-1976, undated (Box 286)
    - Old Indian civil rights addresses, 1975 (Box 286)
    - "Lord's Prayers", undated (Box 286)
    - Addresses of supporters, undated (Box 286)
    - Addresses of Indian AIM, undated (Box 286)
    - Addresses, undated (Box 286)
    - Sound songs, undated (Box 286)
    - Fish poem, undated (Box 286)
    - Lakota songs, undated (Box 286)
    - The songs - Taku Wakan, undated (Box 286)
    - Jean Erdoes - Indian rights letter, undated (Box 286)
    - Janet McCloud, 1984 (Box 286)
    - Jerome Crow Dog, undated (Box 286)
    - Sterilization, 1977 (Box 286)
    - Delphine Eagle Deer, step mother of Jacinta, undated (Box 286)
    - Women, 1969-1993 (Box 286)
    - Women did all the work, undated (Box 286)
    - Dennis Banks affidavit, 1976 (Box 286)
    - Crow Dog philosophizing, undated (Box 286)
    - Quotes, 1977, undated (Box 286)
    - Crow Dog on BIA etc., 1973, undated (Box 286)
    - Funny anonymous quote, undated (Box 287)
    - Philosophy, poem, longhand, undated (Box 287)
    - Soiux words dictionary, undated (Box 287)
    - Sioux words, longhand, undated (Box 287)
    - Steward Rodda, Cherokee, 1975 December 12 (Box 287)
    - Alone on the hilltop, undated (Box 287)
    - Mary pix, undated (Box 287)
    - AIM humor, 1971 undated (Box 287)
    - White policy proposal - AIM humor, undated (Box 287)
    - Jean Erdoes summary, 1976, undated (Box 287)
    - Sing Out, 1976 July 1 (Box 287)
    - Crow Dog's paradise, Peyote and poems, 1977 (Box 287)
    - Annie Mae Pictou Aquash, 1976-1995 (Box 287)
    - Jean - AIM etc., Indian letter, undated (Box 287)
    - Leonard & Vernona at Wounded Knee, undated (Box 287)
    - My Crow Dog poem, undated (Box 287)
    - Sarah Bad Heart Bull, 1974 (Box 287)
    - Banks, 2002 (Box 287)
    - Baldwin, [1975] (Box 287)
    - Bellecourt, 2000-2007 (Box 287)
    - Stan Steiner, 1980-1981 (Box 287)
    - Lame Deer Thanksgiving, undated (Box 287)
    - Tukak, 1983 (Box 287)
    - Lame Deer (German), undated (Box 287)
    - Shelagh Taylor, undated (Box 287)
    - Dan Taylor, 1972-1983 (Box 287)
    - Jack Schwartz, 1991 (Box 287)
    - Geoff Sanborn, 1991 (Box 287)
    - Ann Roberts, 1981 (Box 287)
    - Banks on AIM early, undated (Box 287)
    - Alice Lambert - Bye, bye, Dennis, 1999 (Box 288)
    - Sacred runs - Longest walk, 1996-1997 (Box 288)
    - Banks, 2003 (Box 288)
    - Dennis Banks bio, undated (Box 288)
    - Banks names, 2003, undated (Box 288)
    - Ken Stern, 2002, undated (Box 288)
    - Dennis, 2004 (Box 288)
    - Helga - Sioux, 2002 (Box 288)
    - Kamook, 1998 (Box 288)
    - Fischer Film Linz (German) - article and 3 photographs (photocopies), undated (Box 288)
    - Wind River, undated (Box 288)
    - Odenwald Schule, 1996 (Box 288)
    - Oleg & Wanya, 1997, undated (Box 288)
    - Ghost towns, 1968 (Box 288)
    - Photostats, undated (Box 288)
    - The Silent Singer, undated (Box 288)
    - Government of the white people, undated (Box 288)
    - Iyan Wasichu, undated (Box 288)
    - Janklow Letter, 1976 June (Box 288)
    - Biegert: Only A drop, undated (Box 288)
    - Oda Schottmuller, undated (Box 288)
    - Olguin parole board, undated (Box 288)
    - Ortiz, Resume - Alfonso Ortiz curriculum vitae, undated (Box 288)
    - Alfonso Ortiz, undated (Box 288)
    - Erdoes CV, undated (Box 288)
    - History, General, undated (Box 288)
    - Gila Cliffs, undated (Box 288)
    - Haida, undated (Box 288)
    - Ghost dance, undated (Box 288)
    - German [Sun?] Indian article, undated (Box 288)
    - Fort Robinson, undated (Box 288)
    - Fireland, undated (Box 288)
    - Claus Biegert, 1996 (Box 288)
    - Episcopalian Church, 1973, undated (Box 288)
    - Fictitious Indian, undated (Box 288)
    - Gilcrease Museum, undated (Box 288)
    - Habitat, 1989 (Box 288)
    - Feather laws, undated (Box 288)
    - Drysdale, undated (Box 288)
    - Santana Antonio letter, 1955-1985 (Box 289)
    - Bill Kunstrer obit, undated (Box 289)
    - Jeri-Ahbe-Hill, 1992 (Box 289)
    - May, 1976-1983 (Box 289)
    - Indian Anasazi, 1975 (Box 289)
    - Mokaa, 1992 (Box 289)
    - John Fire Lame Deer - Financial matters, 1971-1979 (Box 289)
    - Crow Dog expenses, 1968-1975 (Box 289)
    - Native American speaker bureau, 1973 (Box 289)
    - Miccosukee, undated (Box 289)
    - Navajo, undated; 2 (Box 289)
    - National Indian Youth Council, 1993, undated (Box 289)
    - National History Museum, undated (Box 289)
    - Mystery Hill, 1971 (Box 289)
    - Indian museums, 1979-1989 (Box 289)
    - Mounds, 1979, undated (Box 289)
    - Native American Church, 1964-1970 (Box 289)
    - Thunder Hawk Brightman, undated (Box 289)
    - Paul Niese Henry, 1981, undated (Box 289)
    - Documents, official, Indian, undated (Box 289)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964, undated (Box 289)
    - US-Sioux Relations - Josephy, 1975, undated (Box 289)
    - Mexico archaeology, 1989 (Box 290)
    - Penna Indians, Pennsylvania, 1986 (Box 290)
    - Anti-Peyote, undated (Box 290)
    - Mohawk, 1972, undated (Box 290)
    - Mississipian Tennessee prehistory, 1989 (Box 290)
    - Maya, 1981-1991 (Box 290)
    - Diseases, 1985-1993 (Box 290)
    - Dance data, 1964 (Box 290)
    - Mexico, undated (Box 290)
    - Storytellers - Red Bird, 1988 September 13 (Box 290)
    - Hidatsa, 1991 August (Box 290)
    - Columbus etc., 1991 (Box 290)
    - Sioux Lakota, 1970-1976 (Box 290)
    - Oklahoma Indians, 1975, undated (Box 290)
    - Navajo code talkers, undated (Box 290)
    - Nevada Indian, undated (Box 290)
    - Leroy Keams, 1967 (Box 290)
    - Good quotes - philosophies, undated (Box 290)
    - Cheyenne letters, 1964, 1977 (Box 290)
    - Cheyenne, 1976 (Box 290)
    - Evonne Wanrow, 1976 (Box 290)
    - "Friends of the Hopi", 1977, undated (Box 290)
    - Indian policy network, 1980, undated (Box 290)
    - Western writers, 1992 (Box 290)
    - Anasazi sites, 1972-1981 (Box 290)
    - Bering land bridge, 1986 (Box 291)
    - Crows, 1978 January 8 (Box 291)
    - Sioux notes, pamphlets, 1966-1973 (Box 291)
    - Mimbres designs, undated (Box 291)
    - Alaska, 1989, undated (Box 291)
    - Apache Arizona, 1976, undated (Box 291)
    - Archaeology, anthropology, 1992 (Box 291)
    - Navajo quotes, undated (Box 291)
    - Plains Indians, undated (Box 291)
    - Cochiti, 1979 (Box 291)
    - Colorado River tribes, undated (Box 291)
    - Chile, undated (Box 291)
    - Brazil paleo, undated (Box 291)
    - Borsany manuscripts, 1987 (Box 291)
    - Sacred objects etc., 1989 (Box 291)
    - Sacred monkey exp., 1977-1979 (Box 291)
    - Seminole - Gore, 1967 (Box 291)
    - Western Shoshone, undated (Box 291)
    - Shoshone, 1990 (Box 291)
    - Europe, undated (Box 291)
    - Squaw's den battle, 1961 (Box 291)
    - Northwest coast, 1989 (Box 291)
    - Bolivia, 1986 (Box 291)
    - Blackfoot Regan stony, 1969-1976 (Box 291)
    - Crow Creek 1400 AD, undated (Box 291)
    - Taos, 1979-1985 (Box 291)
    - Tigua, undated (Box 291)
    - Tipi, undated (Box 291)
    - Tlingit, 1955 (Box 291)
    - Boris Bode, 1995 (Box 291)
    - Bronze Age - Non-Indian, 1979 (Box 292)
    - Columbia River, undated (Box 292)
    - Bodmer, 1985 (Box 292)
    - American Indian Dance Theater, undated (Box 292)
    - Amazon, 1990; 2 (Box 292)
    - Alcohol, 1970 (Box 292)
    - Cheyenne strip mining, 1973 (Box 292)
    - Barry University, 1987, 1993 (Box 292)
    - Taos, undated (Box 292)
    - Chamula, undated (Box 292)
    - Association on American Indian Affairs, 1982 (Box 292)
    - Coal - Bisti badlands, 1982 (Box 292)
    - Inuit Tukak, 1981 (Box 292)
    - Sioux uprising, undated (Box 292)
    - Southwest history, 1939-1940 (Box 292)
    - Peru, Andes gold, 1994. undated (Box 292)
    - Hopi, 1964-1988 (Box 292)
    - Techwa Ikachi, 1976-1977 (Box 292)
    - Black Panther - Kunstler Weinglass, 1969 (Box 292)
    - Eda Gordon, 1999 (Box 292)
    - Newspaper clippings, 2001 (Box 292)
    - Clippings, undated (Box 292)
    - Kimira-Bucholtz - Heaven's Band, manuscripts, undated (Box 292)
    - Helga, 1999 (Box 292)
    - Ferry, 1979-1986 (Box 292)
    - "La Conquista," typescript, notes, synopsis, undated; 3 (Box 293)
    - Amram, 1972-1984 (Box 293)
    - Bartlett, 1972-1978 (Box 293)
    - Nancy Connor, 1999 (Box 293)
    - Carol Ferry, 2001; 2 (Box 293)
    - Angela Wernecke, 1996 (Box 293)
    - Gretchen, 2000 (Box 293)
    - Ferry, Carol & Ping, 1977-1992; 2 (Box 293)
    - Man and marriage, 1963 (Box 293)
    - Tilly Edinger, 1962-1964 (Box 293)
    - Vera Drysdale, 1987 (Box 293)
    - Dokstader, 1970-1992 (Box 293)
    - Mel Bucholtz, Bear poem, undated (Box 293)
    - Dee Brown, 1991 (Box 293)
    - Bedini, 1979-1991 (Box 293)
    - Sterling, undated (Box 293)
    - Note to Cindy and Bill, 1980 (Box 293)
    - Ernest Berke, 1978 (Box 293)
    - Vision proposal, undated (Box 293)
    - Saloons, 1990 (Box 293)
    - Proposal - "Devil's Weed", undated (Box 294)
    - Old curriculum vittae, 1989, undated (Box 294)
    - Santa Fe trial - Signature article, undated (Box 294)
    - Proposal - "Ghosts", undated (Box 294)
    - JAF legends, printed, undated (Box 294)
    - Cosmology proposal, undated (Box 294)
    - Sized art: "American Indian Trickster Tales", undated (Box 294)
    - Gary Farmer - Jean Stawartz, 1991 (Box 294)
    - Saloons, 1998 (Box 294)
    - Indian prisoners religion, undated (Box 294)